(this["webpackJsonpjavascript-quiz"]=this["webpackJsonpjavascript-quiz"]||[]).push([[0],[,,,function(e){e.exports=JSON.parse('[{"questionText":"Which of the following is not a type in JavaScript ?","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"integer","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"number","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"string","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"boolean","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Which of the following is the oldest frontend framework ?","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"Angular","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"React","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Ember","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Backbone","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"Which of the following adds the desired number of elements to the top of an array ?","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"array.unshift()","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"array.pop()","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"array.push()","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"array.splice()","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"What would be the result of 3 + 2 + \' 7 \'?","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"5","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"12","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"57","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"7","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"In JavaScript, which method returns a new array based on the results of running a specified action on each element in the orginal array?","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"reduce","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"map","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"forEach","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"transform","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Which of the following is invalid javaScript for importing from a module ?","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"import * as n2 , { t } from \'./f.js\'","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"import n, { t as t2 } from \'./f.js\'","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"import n, { t } from \'./f.js\'","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"import { default as n2 , t } from \'./f.js\'","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Which of the following is NOT a node.js framework ?","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"Neat","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Sails","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Hapi","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Express","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"What is the result of 100 / 0 in javaScript ?","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"NaN","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"0","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"it throws an error","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Infinity","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"What is the correct way to check for NaN in JavaScript ?","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"isNaN(10)","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"10 == NaN","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"10 === NaN","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"isNumber(10)","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Which of the following is false ?","answerOptions":[{"answerText":" \' \' == false ","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"NaN == NaN","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"false === false","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"null == undefined","isCorrect":false}]}]')},,,,,,,,,function(e,t,s){},function(e,t,s){},function(e,t,s){},function(e,t,s){},function(e,t,s){},function(e,t,s){},function(e,t,s){"use strict";s.r(t);var r=s(1),n=s(0),i=s.n(n),a=s(6),o=s.n(a),c=s(2);s(12);function u(e){var t=e.questions;return Object(r.jsx)(r.Fragment,{children:Object(r.jsx)("div",{className:"question-box",children:Object(r.jsx)("p",{children:t.questionText})})})}s(13);function l(e){var t=e.text,s=e.padding,n=e.width,i=e.onClick;return Object(r.jsx)("div",{children:Object(r.jsx)("button",{onClick:i,className:"btn",style:Object.assign(n,s),children:t})})}s(14);function f(e){var t=e.answers,s=e.setCurrentQuestion,n=e.currentQuestion,i=e.questions,a=e.setShowScore,o=e.setShowQuiz,c=e.setUserScore;return Object(r.jsx)(r.Fragment,{children:Object(r.jsx)("div",{className:"answers-box",children:t.map((function(e){return Object(r.jsx)(l,{onClick:function(){return t=e.isCorrect,n+1<i.length?s((function(e){return e+1})):(a(!0),o(!1)),void(!0===t&&c((function(e){return e+1})));var t},text:e.answerText,padding:{padding:"10px 10px"},width:{width:"100%"}},100*Math.random())}))})})}var x=s(4);s(15);function h(e){var t=e.userScore,s=e.setShowQuiz,n=e.setShowScore,i=e.setUserScore,a=e.setCurrentQuestion,o=e.totalQuestions;return Object(r.jsx)(x.a.div,{className:"container",variants:{visible:{opacity:1},hidden:{opacity:0}},initial:"hidden",animate:"visible",children:Object(r.jsxs)("div",{className:"score-box",children:[Object(r.jsxs)("h1",{children:["you scored ",t," out of ",o]}),Object(r.jsx)(l,{onClick:function(){a(0),i(0),n(!1),s(!0)},text:"try again",padding:{padding:"12px 25px"},width:{width:"auto"}})]})})}function w(e){var t=e.currentQuestion,s=e.totalQuestions;return Object(r.jsx)("div",{children:Object(r.jsxs)("h3",{className:"question-number",children:["Question",Object(r.jsxs)("small",{children:[" ",t+1]}),"/",s]})})}function d(e){var t=e.initialMinute,s=e.initialSeconds,i=e.setShowScore,a=e.setShowQuiz,o=Object(n.useState)(t),u=Object(c.a)(o,2),l=u[0],f=u[1],x=Object(n.useState)(s),h=Object(c.a)(x,2),w=h[0],d=h[1];return Object(n.useEffect)((function(){var e=setInterval((function(){w>0&&d(w-1),0===w&&(0===l?(clearInterval(e),a(!1),i(!0)):(f(l-1),d(59)))}),1e3);return function(){clearInterval(e)}})),Object(r.jsx)("div",{children:Object(r.jsxs)("h3",{className:"timer",children:[l,":",w]})})}s(16);function j(e){var t=e.setShowQuiz,s=e.setShowStart;return Object(r.jsxs)("div",{className:"center",children:[Object(r.jsx)("h1",{className:"title",children:"Javascript Quiz"}),Object(r.jsx)("div",{className:"btn-wrapper",children:Object(r.jsx)(l,{onClick:function(){t(!0),s(!1)},text:"start",padding:{padding:"15px 65px"},width:{width:"auto"}})})]})}var b=s(3);s(17);function p(){var e=Object(n.useState)(!0),t=Object(c.a)(e,2),s=t[0],i=t[1],a=Object(n.useState)(!1),o=Object(c.a)(a,2),l=o[0],p=o[1],O=Object(n.useState)(!1),T=Object(c.a)(O,2),C=T[0],S=T[1],m=Object(n.useState)(0),v=Object(c.a)(m,2),N=v[0],g=v[1],Q=Object(n.useState)(0),q=Object(c.a)(Q,2),y=q[0],k=q[1],z=b.length;return Object(r.jsxs)("div",{className:"bg-gradiant",children:[s&&Object(r.jsx)(j,{setShowQuiz:p,setShowStart:i}),l&&Object(r.jsxs)(x.a.div,{className:"container",variants:{visible:{opacity:1},hidden:{opacity:0}},initial:"hidden",animate:"visible",children:[Object(r.jsxs)("div",{className:"counter",children:[Object(r.jsx)(w,{currentQuestion:y,totalQuestions:z}),Object(r.jsx)(d,{initialMinute:4,initialSeconds:59,setShowScore:S,setShowQuiz:p})]}),Object(r.jsx)(u,{questions:b[y]}),Object(r.jsx)(f,{answers:b[y].answerOptions,setCurrentQuestion:k,currentQuestion:y,questions:b,setShowScore:S,setShowQuiz:p,setUserScore:g})]}),C&&Object(r.jsx)(h,{userScore:N,setShowScore:S,setShowQuiz:p,setUserScore:g,setCurrentQuestion:k,totalQuestions:z})]})}o.a.render(Object(r.jsx)(i.a.StrictMode,{children:Object(r.jsx)(p,{})}),document.getElementById("root"))}],[[18,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.9c0f81ce.chunk.js.map